{
    "subject": "resource/Tomasz_Budzy\u0144ski",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Tarnobrzeg",
    "human_readable": "Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski was born in Tarnobrzeg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9044877290725708,
            "question": "Where was Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8572481870651245,
            "question": "In what year was Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8129372000694275,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7015773057937622,
            "question": "Where did Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6655576825141907,
            "question": "What is Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5407546758651733,
            "question": "Does Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362759232521057,
            "question": "What is Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48036178946495056,
            "question": "Where does Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski currently live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4371480643749237,
            "question": "What are some of Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.395052045583725,
            "question": "Is Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski married?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski was born in Tarnobrzeg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1536_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1536_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski currently live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1536_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1536_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1536_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "yes \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**\n\nConsidering the various transits and their exact dates, it is likely that Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski's life will experience significant changes during specific periods. The conjunction of Mars with Rahu on December 6, 2024, could signal a major event in his life, possibly related to relationships or career development."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document confirms that Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski was indeed born in Tarnobrzeg, Subcarpathian Voivodeship, Poland. Therefore, the statement \"Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski was born in Tarnobrzeg\" is accurate based on the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Yes"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the information given about Tomasz Budzy\u0144ski states that he was born in Tarnobrzeg, but later it mentions that he grew up in Pu\u0142awy and was living in Stanclewo and Warsaw before moving to Pozna\u0144. This implies that his birth place might be different from Tarnobrzeg as stated initially, likely being Pu\u0142awy instead.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}